From the fire, vengeance will rise.
Into the Ashes is a crime, thriller, drama film directed by Aaron Harvey.
With an honest job and a loving wife, Nick Brenner believed he
had safely escaped his violent, criminal history.
But his old crew hasn't forgotten about him or the money he stole, and when they take
what Nick now values the most - his wife - he has nothing left to lose.
Confronted by the town sheriff, who is also his father-in-law, Nick must decide if he will stay on his new
path or indulge in his need for revenge and force his enemies to pay for what they have done.
Nick Brenner, played by Luke Grimes.
Frank Parson, played by Robert Taylor.
Sloan, played by Frank Grillo.
Sal Porter, played by James Badge Dale.
Tara Brenner, played by Marguerite Moreau.
Brad Engels, played by Brady Smith.
Into The Ashes is a 2019 American action thriller film written, produced and directed by Aaron Harvey,
starring Luke Grimes, Frank Grillo, Robert Taylor, James Badge Dale and Marguerite Moreau.
It was released theatrically in the United States
on July 19, 2019, by RLJE Films.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and emotional.